[

](https://www.onlinehsa.com/)

Main Menu

* [Homeowners](https://www.onlinehsa.com/homeowners/)Menu Toggle
* [Real Estate Professionals](https://www.onlinehsa.com/real-estate-agents/)Menu Toggle

* Privacy Policy

**OVERVIEW OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

The chart below provides an overview of the Company’s collection, use and retention practices relating to your personal information. For further detail (including definitions for capitalized terms), please reference the Privacy Policy that follows, including the [Privacy Notice for California, Nebraska, Texas and Virginia Consumers](https://www.onlinehsa.com/state-notice), if applicable to you.

| **Category of Personal Information** | **Sold or Shared** | **Purpose for Collection and Use** | **Retention Practices** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers and Identifying Items | Yes<br><br>Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information | We may use or disclose the personal information we collect: (a) to allow you to register and create an account and profile on the Company Applications (and elsewhere); (b) to fulfill and facilitate any repair or replacement obligations owed to you in connection with any home service plan covering your property, including sending you maintenance communications; (c) to provide you access to the Company Video Services in order for you to communicate with Video Experts who may provide assistance to you for your selected issue; (d) to deliver, provide and process payment for a Product or Service you have requested; (e) to enable you to provide us with feedback; (f) to administer promotions you enter into; (g) to allow your participation in our Communication Services (where available on the Company Applications); (h) to allow your participation in any surveys; (i) to prevent transactional fraud and other illegal activity and to protect the rights, property and safety of us, you and others; (j) to alert you to changes and updates in our Company Applications’ policies, Products or Services; (k) to send you communications (including targeted marketing and promotional offers) that may be of interest to you, such as emails or text messages about Company and its affiliates and subsidiaries and their products or services; (l) to customize, measure and improve products, services, content and advertising, including generating internal reports about the use of our Company Applications; (m) to personalize your overall experience with Company; (n) to enforce our Terms of Use; (o) for testing, research and product development; (p) to respond to law enforcement and regulatory requests, or as required by applicable law, regulation or court order; (q) in connection with a merger, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other transaction involving some or all of our assets that include your information; (r) to provide you financial and investment-related information; (s) for certain other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information; and (t) as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. | We will keep your personal information during the period of your relationship with us and, after that period ends, for as long as is necessary in connection with both our and your legal rights and obligations. This may mean that we keep some types of personal information for longer than others.<br><br>We use the following criteria to determine how long to retain personal information: (a) our relationship with you, and the goods or services we provide to you; (b) any laws or regulations that we are required to follow; (c) whether we are or may be in a legal or other type of dispute with each other or any third party; (d) the type of information that we hold about you; (e) whether we are asked by you or any regulatory authority to keep your personal information for a valid reason, or if we may need to provide it for any legal reasons; and (f) technical considerations and feasibility, and the level of protections in place for your personal information. |
| Commercial Information | No  |
| Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity | Yes<br><br>Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information |
| Sensory Data | No  |
| Inferences from Personal Information Collected | No  |

**PRIVACY POLICY**

 This Privacy Policy is being provided to you by Frontdoor, Inc. (“Frontdoor”), on behalf of itself and certain of its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, the “Company”, “we” or “us”), including its brands American Home Shield (“AHS”), Landmark Home Warranty (“Landmark”), HSA Home Warranty (“HSA”) and OneGuard Home Warranty (“OneGuard”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we receive from or about you, including personally identifiable information, in connection with your access or use of: (a) the websites frontdoor.com, frontdoorhome.com, ahs.com, landmarkhw.com, onlinehsa.com and oneguardhomewarranty.com (together with any successor websites, the “Sites”), (b) other interactive properties, including, but not limited to, the Frontdoor® mobile application or the mobile application of other brands (each, an “App,” and together with the Sites, the “Company Applications”), (c) the products and services provided by the Company, including through the Company Applications or offline (the “Product(s)” and “Service(s)”), (d) offline communications with the Company, including direct mail, telephone and postal mail and (e) any other means or applications in which you connect with the Company or a third party from whom the Company receives information about you.

By accessing or using the Company Applications or our Products and Services, registering with, providing personal information to, or communicating with, the Company, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use, storage and transfer (including international transfer) of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. THIS PRIVACY POLICY AFFECTS YOUR RIGHTS AND LIABILITIES UNDER THE LAW. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not access or use the Company Applications, provide us with personal information or otherwise communicate with us.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may collect different types of information about you, depending upon how you interact with us. This information may include personal information, Financial Information, demographic information, log-in information and Device information. Sometimes we collect combinations of all these types of information or aggregate some or all of these types of information to improve the Products and Services and facilitate other legitimate business purposes. In each case, when using the Company Applications, it is indicated on the Company Applications whether any personal information or demographic data must be provided for you to access and use the Company Applications or purchase the requested Product or Service.

**Connecting with the Company Applications and Information Provided by You**

**When You Register or Otherwise Contact Us.**  When you provide us with information (including personal information) in connection with a particular activity, you agree that such action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to receiving communications from the Company (and its affiliates and subsidiaries) through the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide the authorization to contact you. This means the Company may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving.

**Registration Information.** We will collect personal information from you if you register on the Company Applications or place an order for our Products or Services, which may include, but is not limited to, name, address, phone number(s), and email address(es). You may not use a user/account name that is vulgar or otherwise offensive (as determined by the Company), infringes any trademark or other proprietary rights of others, or is used in any way that violates the applicable terms and conditions governing Products or Services accessible through the Company Applications or otherwise (collectively, and as applicable to specific Products and Services, the “Terms of Use”). The Company reserves the right to deny, in its sole discretion, any user access to the Company Applications or our Products and Services without notice, for any or no reason.

**Financial Information.** Financial information is information that you provide to us, including your bank account number, routing number, debit or credit card number and related billing information (collectively, the “Financial Information”). We require such Financial Information in order to process payment for the purchase of a Product or Service that you have requested. By submitting your Financial Information, you consent to our providing your Financial Information to those Authorized Third Party Service Providers as are reasonably necessary to support and process your transactions as well as your credit card issuer and banking institution. We ask that you do not enter Financial Information into your profile, except in the fields provided for that information.

**Facebook.** You may be given the option to link your Facebook account so that you can comment on the Company Applications and your interaction with the Company or take advantage of other features of the Company Applications. When you comment on the Company Applications using your Facebook username and password and click “allow” on the Facebook permission authorization screen, we will automatically import all information that you allow to be imported from your Facebook profile based upon your privacy settings at Facebook, such as your interests, _etc._ (collectively, “Permitted Facebook Profile Content”) and you give us permission and consent to:  (a) capture, record, store, use and display your Permitted Facebook Profile Content, including syncing access to such Permitted Facebook Profile Content when you are not using Company Applications and (b) otherwise use Permitted Facebook Profile Content as described in this Privacy Policy. The authentication of your Facebook login credentials is conducted solely through Facebook.

**User Generated Content.** The Company Applications may contain review or chat areas or other message, communication or other mechanisms designed to enable you to communicate with the Company (including through the Video Services), others or to post content on the Company Applications (the “Communication Services”). Please remember that any information you disclose while participating with the Communication Services becomes public information, becomes the property of, and is subject to redistribution by, the Company. You should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting. There is no expectation of privacy when posting or otherwise participating on the Communication Services. If you post content, such as messages, reviews or photos, please be aware that any personally identifiable information contained in such content is accessible to registered users or visitors to that Company Application or Communication Service and we have no control over how those users may use your personally identifiable information. We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor any activity and content associated with the Communication Services. We reserve the right to take action in connection with any content, including that which we deem inappropriate. Please review our Terms of Use for more information regarding your appropriate use of these Communication Services.

**Video Services**.  The Company Applications may provide you access to certain video chat services (“Video Services”) to communicate with the Company’s video experts (“Video Experts”) who may provide assistance for your selected issue. Please note that your use of the Video Services is subject to the Terms of Use.

**Information Collected Through Technology**

In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies such as cookies, mobile tracking mechanisms, pixel tags, server-side tracking mechanisms, web beacons, browser analysis tools, and web server logs to track and record certain information, including as relates to your use of the Company Applications. As you use our Company Applications, your browser, devices and server (and technologies imbedded in your browser, devices and server) communicate with mechanisms operated by us, our business partners and our service providers to coordinate and record your activity and fulfill your requests (“Usage Information”). We collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies. For example, we may collect information from the devices you use to access our Company Applications, your operating system type or mobile device model, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. In addition, we collect your IP address or other unique identifier (“Device Identifier”) from your computer or mobile device used to access the Company Applications (each, a “Device”). A Device Identifier is a number that is assigned to the Device used to access the Company Applications, and our systems identify your Device by its Device Identifier. We may also collect information about the website you were visiting before you came to our Company Applications and the website you visit after you leave our Company Applications, if this information is supplied to us by your browser, Device or otherwise. We may use this Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance or otherwise improve the Company Applications.

The information from cookies and related technology is stored in web server logs and also in web cookies and other tracking mechanisms kept on your Device(s), which are then transmitted back to the Company Applications. These servers are operated, and the cookies and other tracking mechanisms managed, by us, our business partners or our service providers. For example, when you visit Company Applications, we and our service providers may place cookies or other tracking mechanisms on your Device(s). Cookies and other tracking mechanisms allow us to recognize you when you return to a Company Application and may track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies and other tracking mechanisms also help us detect certain kinds of fraud. “Cookies” and similar tracking mechanisms use a small amount of information that is sent to your browser, server or Device to store information about your account, your preferences, and your use of the Company Applications.

Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on the Company Applications or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed specific actions (for example, opening an email). When you access the Company Applications or open email messages, the pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action to us, or our service providers. These tools allow us to measure responses to our communications and improve the Company Applications and promotions.

We also use embedded scripts which are programming codes designed to collect information about your interactions with the Company Applications, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Company Applications and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

We use HTML5 features for data collection, tracking, and storage in our apps for mobile devices. HTML5 offers methods like LocalStorage, SessionStorage, and IndexedDB that provide alternatives to traditional browser cookies. These HTML5 storage methods can be used to store data and track user interactions across sessions but are not stored in the browser’s cookie files. Users can manage and delete HTML5 storage through their browser settings, app-specific settings, or LocalStorage on their mobile devices.

In many cases, the information we collect using cookies and other similar tools is used in non-identifiable ways, without any reference to information that could reasonably identify you. For example, we use information we collect about Company Application users to optimize our Products and Services and understand traffic and usage patterns. In other cases, we associate the information we collect using cookies and related technologies with personal information. Whenever we associate Usage Information or a Device Identifier with your personal information, we will treat it as personal information.

**Information You Provide About a Third Party**

If you send someone else a communication from the Company Applications, such as sending an invitation to a friend, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses, _etc._) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Company Applications, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

**Information We Collect from Third Parties**

We may receive personal information from third parties who have purchased on your behalf, or recommended to you, our Products and Services (for example, Products and Services purchased by realtors who sold or rented you your home), which may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, phone number(s), and email address(es). We also acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information you have provided or that we collected automatically, such as information to validate or update your address or other demographic and lifestyle information. We use this information to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect, to target our communications so that the Company can inform you of products, services and offers that may be of interest to you and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

**HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

The Company uses your information (including your personal information), subject to applicable laws, for the following purposes:

1. to allow you to register and create an account and profile on the Company Applications (and elsewhere);
2. to fulfill and facilitate any repair or replacement obligations owed to you in connection with any home service plan covering your property, incuding sending you maintenance communications;
3. to provide you access to Company Video Services in order for you to communicate with Video Experts who may provide assistance to you for your selected issue;
4. to deliver, provide and process payment for a Product or Service you have requested;
5. to enable you to provide us with feedback;
6. to administer promotions you enter into;
7. to allow your participation in our Communication Services (where available on the Company Applications);
8. to allow your participation in any surveys;
9. to prevent transactional fraud and other illegal activity and to protect the rights, property and safety of us, you and others;
10. to alert you to changes and updates in our Company Applications’ policies, Products or Services;
11. to send you communications (including targeted marketing and promotional offers) that may be of interest to you, such as emails or text messages about the Company and its affiliates and subsidiaries and their products or services;
12. to customize, measure and improve products, services, content and advertising, including generating internal reports about the use of our Company Applications;
13. to personalize your overall experience with the Company;
14. to enforce our Terms of Use;
15. for testing, research and product development;
16. to respond to law enforcement and regulatory requests, or as required by applicable law, regulation or court order;
17. in connection with a merger, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other transaction involving some or all of our assets that include your information;
18. to provide you financial and investment-related information;
19. for certain other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information; and
20. as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Transactional Communications.** We may send you communications from time to time relating to your account, orders and other transactional matters involving the Company (or its affiliates and subsidiaries). These communications may include requests, order confirmations, invoices, renewals or customer service notifications. We may also send you service-related announcements; for instance, if our Services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, the delivery of a Product is delayed or there is some service issue with an item you may have ordered. You may not opt out of receiving these communications, as they are not promotional in nature.

**Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** We may use third party service providers (“Authorized Third Party Service Providers”) to help us operate our business and the Company Applications or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your information with these Authorized Third Party Service Providers.

**Third Parties Who Recommended our Products and Services****.** From time to time we may provide to third parties who either purchased on your behalf, or recommended our Products and Services to you (such as realtors who sold or rented you your home), information regarding your use of those Products or Services.

**Electronic and Direct Mail Promotional Offers.** The Company and our affiliates and subsidiaries may send you promotional emails and direct mailings regarding special offers about our Products and Services or on behalf of third party marketing partners that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive emails or direct mail regarding special promotions or offers you may opt-out as provided in the CHOICE AND OPT OUT section below.

**Telemarketing.** If you have given us your telephone number, the Company and our affiliates and subsidiaries may use the telephone number you provided to contact you, including to (a) follow up on your order and (b) market to you renewals or other Products or Services. If you would prefer not to receive marketing phone calls from us, you may opt-out as provided in the CHOICE AND OPT OUT section below.

**Co-Branded Areas.** Certain areas on our Company Applications may be provided to you in association with third parties such as advertisers that provide products and services or rewards programs (“Co-Branded Areas”). Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the applicable third party. If you elect to register for the products or services provided at these Co-Branded Areas, you either will be providing your personal information to both us and the applicable third party or we may be providing your personal information directly to such third party. With respect to Co-Branded Areas, your information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties and we suggest you review the individual privacy policies of each company with whom you establish a relationship (including those third party sponsors or advertisers within a Co-Branded Area).

**Feedback.** All comments, feedback or materials submitted by you to us, including feedback, testimonials, images, reviews, questions, comments, suggestions or ideas (collectively, “Feedback”), shall be received and treated by us on a non-confidential and unrestricted basis (except to the extent such Feedback is subject to certain restrictions under applicable law). In accordance with all applicable law and this Privacy Policy, the Company and its affiliates and subsidiaries will be free to use, display, perform, distribute, copy, adapt, and promote, in any medium now known or later developed, without compensation to you, the Feedback along with all ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques or methodologies contained in such Feedback, for any purpose whatsoever, including without limitation, developing, marketing and selling our Products and Services incorporating such Feedback. You agree that in submitting Feedback, such Feedback will not violate any right of any third party, including any confidentiality, copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or intellectual property or proprietary rights, and will not cause injury to any person or entity. You further agree that no Feedback you submit will contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, threatening, abusive or obscene material, or contain viruses, commercial solicitations, or any form of “spam.”

**Promotions.** We may offer promotions (each, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern such Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, personal information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules. In addition, if you choose to enter a Promotion, the personal information you provide to us will be used by us in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Legal Matters; Safety.** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you (including, without limitation, the contents of any video, chat, messaging, or other communication posted in or made available through the Communication Services), and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), including to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Use or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, in accordance with all applicable law and this Privacy Policy, we may disclose your information and communications in situations that we believe to be:  (a) emergencies involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property if we believe that your information in any way relates to that threat or (b) inappropriate with respect to your conduct on the Company Applications or when using the Communication Services.

**Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets.** In the event that we, or any of our businesses, are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personally identifiable information (including all personal information) of our customers and visitors to our Company Applications may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. In addition, information about our customers and registered users may also be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, support or funding.

**Mobile Information.**  No mobile information will be shared by us with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes. Text messaging originator opt-in data and consent will not be shared with any third parties unless required by law.

**Third Party Analytic Technologies and Interest-Based Advertising**

We may allow third-party companies to serve ads or collect certain information on our behalf when you visit the Company Applications. We use these third-party companies’ ad services, analytic, measurement, attribution and tracking tools to facilitate our provision of certain advertisements for our Products and Services and to better understand who is using the Company Applications, how people are using the Company Applications, how to improve the effectiveness of the Company Applications and their content and how to serve more targeted advertising to you. These third-party companies may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the Company Applications, Device Identifiers, type of operating system used and other website(s) or mobile applications you may have visited. They might combine information they collect from your interaction with Company Applications with information they collect from other sources and use this combined information to send you certain marketing or other communications.

If you would like more information about the Company’s use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept the cookies used to track certain of your activities, you can go to the footer of the Frontdoor, AHS, Landmark, HSA or OneGuard webpage, as applicable, and click on the “Cookie Settings” link. If you wish to exercise choice with respect to collection and use of your data by certain third-party tools, you may visit: [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Some of the analytics, tracking and advertising tools we may use are Google Analytics and Google Ads. The Google Analytics and Google Ads features we may use include the following:

* Remarketing on the Google Display Network;
* Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting; and
* Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and other identifiers.

Certain of the technologies described above may be managed by users; if you wish to manage your Google accounts and the way certain advertising practices may be applied to those accounts, you may visit: [https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). Additionally, if you wish to learn more about Google’s advertising practices, you may visit: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en)

If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available at: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

We use Meta Pixel, a web analytics and advertising service provided by Meta, Inc. (“Meta”), in the Company Applications. The data from Meta Pixel is also saved and processed by Meta. Meta can connect this data with your Meta account and use it for its own and others’ advertising purposes, in accordance with Meta’s Privacy Policy found at [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). Please click [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads#\_=\_](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads#_=_) if you would like to withdraw your consent for use of your data with Meta Pixel.

We also partner with Microsoft Clarity and Microsoft Advertising to capture how you use and interact with our website through behavioral metrics, heatmaps and session replay to improve and market our Products and Services. Website usage data is captured using first and third-party cookies and other tracking technologies to determine the popularity of Products and Services and online activity. Additionally, we use this information for site optimization, fraud and security purposes and advertising. For more information about how Microsoft collects and uses your data, visit https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement.

**ACCESS TO AND DELETION OF YOUR INFORMATION**

In addition to any rights you may have under applicable state law (as described under “Important Disclosures, Practices and Contact Information” below), if you have an online account or an App account with us, you may deactivate or otherwise manage your account at any time by visiting the Company Applications.

If for any reason you wish to change the personal information or Financial Information you provided to us, you may do so within the Company Applications. For example, if you are an App user, you may delete your App account data by selecting “Delete My Account” in the “My membership plan” area within the App.

If you delete or deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms of Use or other policies, take actions we deem necessary due to technical and legal requirements, and as dictated by constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our Company Applications. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ privacy practices.

**CHOICE AND OPT OUT**

To opt-out of marketing communications or to request to be added to our Do Not Call List or our Do Not Mail List, you may use one of these convenient methods:

**Electronic Promotional Offers.** If you do not want to receive emails regarding special promotions or offers, you may: (a) click the unsubscribe link  in the footer of any email or (b) contact our Privacy Coordinator at the address set forth below.

**Direct Mail Promotional Offers.**  If you do not want to receive promotional offers through direct mail, you may contact our Privacy Coordinator at the address set forth below.

**Telemarketing.**  If you do not want to receive marketing phone calls, you may: (a) ask to be placed on our Do Not Call list when you receive a call from us or (b) contact our Privacy Coordinator at the address set forth below.

**SMS** **Programs.** In the event you elect to receive certain notices and announcements via text message (SMS) through the Company’s service notification program or promotional text program respectively, you can opt out of continuing to receive these communications through SMS by texting STOP to the SMS number used by the Company to contact you. You can also call 1-844-521-1325 or contact our Privacy Coordinator at the address set forth below.

**Push Notifications.** If you wish to change your preference with respect to receiving push notifications within the Company Applications, you can opt out of receiving those communications within the Company Applications.

**Brand-Specific Communications.** If you receive marketing communications from individual brands (e.g., AHS, Landmark, HSA and OneGuard), you must opt-out individually from each of the brands from which you are receiving brand-specific marketing communications.

**Service Communications.** Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional electronic or direct mail offers, we may continue to send you service notifications by email or direct mail that are related to your account(s) and our Products and Services you have requested or in which you are currently enrolled.

**IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

**Links to other Website(s) and Communities.** To the extent hyperlinks may be utilized to access external or third-party website(s) and communities, you should be aware that these external or third-party website(s) and communities are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of each such website and community to determine how your information will be utilized.

**Security.** We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Company Applications, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also, we advise that you log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to a Company Application. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

**California, Nebraska, Texas and Virginia Resident Privacy Rights.** If you are a California, Nebraska, Texas or Virginia resident, applicable law may provide you with additional privacy rights with respect to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. For more information, visit our [Privacy Notice for California, Nebraska, Texas and Virginia Consumers](https://www.onlinehsa.com/state-notice/).

**A Note to International Users.** The Company Applications are operated in the United States. If you are located anywhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to, processed and stored in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Company Applications or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States. You are also consenting to the application of United States federal and Tennessee state law in all matters concerning the Company Applications and this Privacy Policy.

**Children’s Privacy.** The Company Applications are generally intended for general adult audiences and are not directed or intended for children under sixteen years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under sixteen years of age. If you are under sixteen years of age, you should not register or provide personal information on the Company Applications. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user who has provided personal information is under sixteen years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s personal information from our systems. Additionally, we do not knowingly sell or share personal information of individuals who are under sixteen years of age.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Company Applications, with the “Effective Date” posted within the Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new Company Applications or Communication Services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, you will know either because (a) the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy will change or (b) we will provide you with a copy of the updated Privacy Policy that includes an updated Effective Date. By accessing the Company Applications or interacting with us after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current Privacy Policy for information captured after the Effective Date of that Privacy Policy.

**Disputes.** If you choose to visit the Company Applications your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the United States and the State of Tennessee.

**No Rights of Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Company Applications.

**Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of the Company Applications and Communication Services, please email us at [privacy@frontdoor.com](mailto:privacy@frontdoor.com) or write to us at:

Legal Department  
Attn: Privacy Coordinator  
Frontdoor  
3400 Players Club Parkway, Suite 300  
Memphis, TN 38125

_(Last updated_ _September__, 2024)_

* * *

---------------------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------------------------

Contractors
-----------

**Our Company**  

**Other Frontdoor™ Sites**  

© 2024 Home Security of America, Inc. All rights reserved.
